<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ubiratan Soares</title>
    <link>https://ubiratansoares.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ubiratan Soares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ubiratansoares.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>https://ubiratansoares.github.io/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubiratansoares.github.io/talks/</guid>
      <description>In the year of 2012, I was already working professionaly with Software development for a while and I decided that I could try a lightning talk - only 15 terrifying minutes !!! - at The Developers Conference, one of the largest software development conferences hosted in Brazil.
It would be my first public talk about software development; and besides the fact I worked as a partial time teacher before, I was really scared to present something in public, eventually facing people that knew so much more than me on the chosen topic &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://ubiratansoares.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubiratansoares.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR
My very first interest on computers dates from my teenage years, when the hard drive from my first PC died. I was 12 years old, and while trying to get some fix to my computer, I felt myself ashmed because someone told me that &amp;ldquo;the issue is the hard drive and the fix will cost you this!&amp;rdquo; and I could not do anything about it &amp;hellip; because I did not know what a Hard Drive were or meant &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uma despedida, ou quase isso</title>
      <link>https://ubiratansoares.github.io/post/gdgsp-goodbye/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ubiratansoares.github.io/post/gdgsp-goodbye/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;No sábado do dia 10 de junho de 2017, eu conduzi meu último evento como organizador &lt;em&gt;de facto&lt;/em&gt; do Google Developers Group de São Paulo. Foi a edição número #48 - especial de quatro anos !!! - do Android Meetup, possivelmente o mais antigo evento recorrente de Android do país.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>